# 哈喽 大家好
Hello
# 我是王刚
I am Wang Gang
# 最近停更了（做菜视频）差不多有10天半个月了吧
I haven’t uploaded cooking videos for about half a month.
# 这些时间粉丝也在问我
Fans also have been asking me
# 这段时间到底在干什么
What was I doing during this time
# 其实我想跟大家说我一刻也没有闲着
I what to tell you all that I was busy working
# 然后这边的话是我们的厨房
This is our kitchen
# 现在已经全部ok了
It’s all done and ready now
# 这里其实已经拍了一期视频了
We have already shot a video here
# 这是电影机的三脚架
This is the tripod for the movie camera
# 这个箱子是专门装电影机的
This box is for the movie camera
# 那个是装微单的
That one is for the mirrorless camera
# 这里有一些三脚架一些灯
Here are some tripods and lights
# 还有一些厨具已经全部到了
And some of the cooking equipment has arrived
# 然后昨天拍了一期
And we shot one video yesterday
# 现在在做后期
We are doing post-production now
# 其实这个后期流程比较复杂
The process of post-production is actually complex
# 是非常麻烦的
It’s really a big deal
# 大家过来这边看一下
Let’s take a cook here
# 我这边总共有三台这个炒菜的灶
I have three wok ranges
# 就是炒菜的灶
Ranges for cooking
# 大家会问我这个
People ask me
# 其实用这么多灶来干什么
Why so many stations
# 就是为了以后这里成熟了之后
When the business is mature here
# 可以到时候接待粉丝什么的过来吃大餐
We can host fans for a feast here
# 是没有问题的
There’s no problem
# 其实我拍视频只要一台就够了
Actually one would be enough for making videos
# 为什么买这么多
Then why did I buy so many?
# 就是想着吧 想法总是美好的
I was thinking... I have some ideals
# 是吧
Things that I look forward to
# 多招几个徒弟啊
Recruit a few more apprentices
# 有用的徒弟
Useful apprentices
# 男徒弟过来学厨艺
Male apprentices coming here to learn how to cook
# 学好了之后
When they are skilful enough,
# 接待一下粉丝也挺好玩的
it would be fun to host our fans
# 这个是补光灯
This is the fill-light
# 然后我这边
And here is
# 是切菜的地方
A placing for cutting ingredients
# 像这个砧板也换了一个
We got a new cutting board
# 因为原先的砧板
Because the old cutting board
# 特别容易发霉
is really easy to go moldy
# 现在是用的这种更硬一点的
Now we are using the harder one
# 更耐用一点
It can last longer
# 然后这边是两个补光灯
There are two fill-lights
# 其实为什么换这么大的工作室的原因就是
The reason why we moved into this big studio is that
# 原先的工作室这一面是靠墙的
In the old studio, this side was leaning against the wall
# 我想做一些补光
I wanted to fill in the light,
# 想换一些长焦镜头是根本就没有位置
but there was no room for long lenses
# 所以
So
# 这边然后是两个冰箱
Here are two friges
# 现在只开了一个
Only one is operating
# 放的食材什么的都比较少
We haven't put many ingredients in here
# 现在只是说开了运行一下
It’s operating for testing
# 然后下面放了一些菜
And down here are some dishes
# 这些菜目前就是我跟摄影师
These dishes are for the photographer and me
# 上午过来拍 拍到中午之后 我们就自己炒了
We came here and filmed before noon.
# 炒点菜在这里吃了
Then we cooked some dishes here for lunch
# 然后吃完饭下午又接着干
Then we continue working after lunch
# 然后这一台的话暂时还没有用
This one hasn’t been put into use yet
# 这些也是全新的
All those are brand new
# 然后这边还有一个六眼灶
And here is a range with six burners
# 就跟我那边差不多吧
It’s similar to the one I used before
# 六眼灶买来就是拍一些比较
This six-burner range is for the more home-style dishes
# 更加家常的做一些煲仔呀煲汤之类的就在这边做
Such as clay pot dishes and and soups. These will be cooked here
# 现在整体做了一天
Now everything has been put into operation for a day
# 昨天拍了一期感觉这个
We shot a video yesterday
# 这边特别湿啊特别回潮
I feel that it’s really humid around here
# 蚊子特别多
A lot of mosquitoes
# 其他都还好
Everything else has been fine
# 然后这里空间也够高
And the space is tall enough
# 然后
And
# 布局也比较好
Great layout
# 就感觉做起来更加得心应手吧
I can work more efficiently and enjoyably
# 嗯 昨天拍了第一期
Well, we shot our first video here yesterday
# 虽然说拍得很辛苦
Although it was tough work
# 扛着个电影机还有那三角架加起来肯定有30多斤
Carrying the cinema camera and that tripod, they must add up to 30 jin (15kg)
# 扛着跑来跑去的
Running around with that
# 然后这些灯啊
And all these lights
# 第一天拍遇到了不少麻烦
A lot of headaches on our first day of shooting
# 不过这些都是小问题
But these are all small problems
# 特别容易就克服了
Super easy to overcome
# 小小的问题
Small problems
# 难不倒我们
Won’t beat us
# 然后这边
And here
# 明天吧
Tomorrow
# 明天我们的视频做菜的视频就会更新
Our cooking tutorial videos will be uploaded tomorrow
# 但是第一期我们没有做菜
But it won't be a savoury dish
# 第一期用冰糖
We used Chinese rock sugar
# 用糖拍了一期
for that video
# 你们可以先猜一下我们拍的是什么
You can try to guess what recipe the next video will be
# 呃 好了
Well, okay then
# 本期视频就到这里
That's all for this video
# 以后的话会在这里产出更多质量更高的内容
We will continue to produce more content with higher quality here
# 就到这里 拜拜
That's all. Bye.